Toni Morrison Papers, 1957-: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Writings, 1929 September-2015; 100 boxes (3 partial)
  - Subseries 1: Novels, 1929 September-2015; 66 boxes (4 partial)
    - God Help the Child, 2012 December 21-2015; 4 boxes
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 19)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 20)
        Pages 60-86.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 21)
        Pages 98-103.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 64, Folder 22)
        Pages 98-99.
      - Draft, May 18; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 23)
        Pages 1-136.
      - Draft, June 14; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Draft, June 26; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 65, Folder 2)
        Pages 1-179.
      - Draft, July 23; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 65, Folder 3)
        Pages 151-154.
      - Draft, July 25; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 65, Folder 4)
        Pages 171-188.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 65, Folder 5)
        Pages 1-215.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 65, Folder 6)
        Pages 1-208.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 65, Folder 7)
        Pages 1-232.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 66, Folder 1)
        Pages 1-233.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 66, Folder 2)
        Inserts.
      - Setting Copy, circa 2014; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Page Proofs, 2014 November 4; 1 item (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - First Pass Master Page Proofs, 2014 November 4; 1 item (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Second Pass Master Page Proofs, 2015 January 15; 1 item (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Laser Proofs, 2015 February 11; 1 item (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Page Layout Samples, circa 2015; 1 item (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Phase 2: Children's Literature, 1998-2014; 3 boxes
    - The Big Box, 1998-1999; 3 folders (Box CL 1, Folder 1-3)
      Written with Slade Morrison and illustrated by Giselle Potter. Contains typescript and printout drafts with revisions and page proofs.
    - The Book of Mean People, 1999-2002; 4 folders (Box CL oversize 1, Folder 1-4, Box CL oversize 2, Folder 1, Box CL 1, Folder 4-9)
      Written with Slade Morrison and illustrated by Pascal Lemaitre. Contains autograph legal pad and printout drafts, oversize artwork, and page proofs.
    - Who's Got Game?, 2002-2010; 4 folders (Box CL oversize 1, Folder 5-8, Box CL 1, Folder 10-20, Box CL 2, Folder 1)
      Written with Slade Morrison and illustrated by Pascal Lemaitre. Series of retold Aesop's fables including Ant or the Grasshopper? (2003), Lion or the Mouse? (2003), Poppy or the Snake? (2003), published individually and as a 3-story compilation in 2005; Tortoise or the Hare? (2010). Autograph legal pad drafts, printouts with revisions, oversize artwork and page proofs. Also includes notes, drafts, and sketches for story ideas never published, including The Mirror or the Glass? and a version of "The Goose who Laid the Golden Eggs."
    - Remember: The Journey to School Integration, circa 2004; 1 folder (Box CL 2, Folder 2)
      Contains autograph legal pad drafts.
    - Peeny Butter Fudge, circa 2009-2011; 2 folders (Box CL oversize 1, Folder 9-10, Box CL 2, Folder 3)
      Written with Slade Morrison and illustrated by Joe Cepeda. Contains autograph legal pad drafts, samples of the miniature bilingual edition in English and Spanish, oversize artwork, and a Cheerios box with mini book enclosed.
    - Little Cloud and Lady Wind, circa 2010; 1 folder (Box CL 2, Folder 4)
      Written with Slade Morrison and illustrated by Sean Qualls. Contains autograph legal pad and printout drafts with revisions.
    - Please Louise, 2014; 1 folder (Box CL oversize 1, Folder 11, Box CL oversize 2, Folder 2)
      Written with Slade Morrison and illustrated by Shadra Strickland. Contains autograph legal pad drafts, oversize artwork and page samples.
  - Phase 2: Short Fiction, 1957-2003; 9 boxes (1 partial)
    Autograph notepad pages and typescripts (original and photocopied). "Two of Eves" is an early version of The Bluest Eye.
    This series is available only via digital access in the reading room.
    - "Ma Cher", 1957; 1 folder (Box SF1, Folder 1)
    - "Chloe", undated; 1 folder (Box SF1, Folder 2)
    - "The Sound of Lilacs", undated; 1 folder (Box SF1, Folder 3)
    - "Ours is not the worst...", undated; 1 item (Box SF1, Folder 4)
    - "Gia", undated; 1 folder (Box SF1, Folder 5)
    - "Two of Eves", undated; 1 folder (Box SF1, Folder 6)
    - "Recitatif", 1981-1990; 1 folder (Box SF1, Folder 7)
      Includes correspondence with Lynn Nesbit of ICM and Jean Herskovits.
    - Phase 2: Non-fiction, 1970-2003; 8 boxes (1 partial)
      - Playing in the Dark, 1989-2001; 2 boxes (1 partial)
        Originally delivered in 1990 as a series of three William E. Massey Lectures at Harvard. First published as excerpt "Black Matter(s)" in Grand Street magazine in 1991 then in full as Playing in the Dark in 1992 by Harvard University Press. See also Studies in American Africanism materials in Series TK: Teaching Files.
        - Massey Lecture Notes, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box PD1, Folder 1)
          Available only via digital access in the reading room.
        - Drafts, circa 1989-1991; 15 folders Printouts, corrected. (Box PD1, Folder 2-16, Box PD2, Folder 17)
        - Setting Copy, 1992; 1 item (Box PD2, Folder 2)
          With correspondence from Harvard University Press.
        - F&Gs, 1992; 1 item (Box PD2, Folder 3)
        - Grand Street, 1991; 1 folder (Box PD2, Folder 4)
        - Harvard University Press, 1991-1992; 1 box (Box PD2, Box 5)
        - Vintage, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box PD2, Folder 6)
        - Picador, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box PD2, Folder 7)
        - Press, 1992-2001; 1 folder (Box PD2, Folder 8)
      - Race-ing Justice, En-Gendering Power, 1991-2003; 3 boxes
        - Homi Bhaba, 1992; 1 folder (Box RJ1, Folder 1)
        - Claudia Brodsky Lacour, 1991; 1 folder (Box RJ1, Folder 2)
        - Margaret Burnham, 1991; 1 folder (Box RJ1, Folder 3)
        - Kimberle Crenshaw, 1992; 1 folder (Box RJ1, Folder 4)
        - Paula Giddings, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box RJ1, Folder 5)
        - Leon Higginbotham, Jr., 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box RJ1, Folder 6)
        - Wahneema Lubiano, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box RJ1, Folder 7)
        - Manning Marable, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box RJ1, Folder 8)
        - Nellie McKay, 1991; 1 folder (Box RJ1, Folder 9)
        - Toni Morrison, circa 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box RJ1, Folder 10)
        - Nell Painter, undated; 1 folder (Box RJ2, Folder 1)
        - Gayle Pemberton, 1991; 1 folder (Box RJ2, Folder 2)
        - Andrew Ross, 1991; 1 folder (Box RJ2, Folder 3)
        - Christine Stansell, undated; 1 folder (Box RJ2, Folder 4)
        - Carol Swain, 1991; 1 folder (Box RJ2, Folder 5)
        - Michael Thelwell, undated; 1 folder (Box RJ2, Folder 6)
        - Kendall Thomas, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box RJ2, Folder 7)
        - Cornel West, undated; 1 folder (Box RJ2, Folder 8)
        - Patricia Williams, 1991; 1 folder (Box RJ2, Folder 9)
        - Page Proofs, 1992; 1 item (Box RJ2, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence, 1991-1992; 2 folders (Box RJ2, Folder 11-12)
        - Pantheon, 1991-2003; 1 folder (Box RJ2, Folder 13)
        - Chatto & Windus, 1992; 1 folder (Box RJ3, Folder 1)
        - Philadelphia Forum, 1992; 1 folder (Box RJ3, Folder 2)
        - Publicity, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box RJ3, Folder 3)
        - Press, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box RJ3, Folder 4)
      - Birth of a Nation'hood, 1995-1998; 3 boxes
        Edited with Claudia Brodsky Lacour.
        - Research Material, 1995-1997; 2 folders (Box BN1, Folder 1-2)
        - O.J. Project, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box BN1, Folder 3)
          Includes book outlines and correspondence with contributors.
        - Contributors, circa 1996; 1 folder (Box BN1, Folder 4)
        - Reimbursables O.J., 1996; 1 folder (Box BN1, Folder 5)
        - Submissions, 1996; 1 folder (Box BN1, Folder 6)
        - Homi Bhabha, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box BN1, Folder 7)
        - Claudia Brodsky Lacour, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box BN1, Folder 8)
        - Drucilla Cornell, 1996; 1 folder (Box BN1, Folder 9)
        - Kimberle Crenshaw, 1996; 1 folder (Box BN1, Folder 10)
        - Ann duCille, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box BN2, Folder 1-2)
        - Jacques Derrida, 1996; 1 folder (Box BN2, Folder 3)
        - Leon Higginbotham Jr., 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box BN2, Folder 4)
        - George Lipsitz, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box BN2, Folder 5)
        - Erroll McDonald, 1996; 1 folder (Box BN2, Folder 6)
        - Toni Morrison, 1996; 1 folder (Box BN2, Folder 7)
        - Ishmael Reed, 1996; 1 folder (Box BN2, Folder 8)
        - Dave Roediger, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box BN2, Folder 9)
        - Andrew Ross, 1996; 1 folder (Box BN2, Folder 10)
        - Armond White, 1996; 1 folder (Box BN2, Folder 11)
        - Patricia Williams, 1996; 1 folder (Box BN3, Folder 1)
        - Setting Copy, 1997 July 21; 1 item (Box BN3, Folder 2-3)
        - Publicity, 1997; 1 folder (Box BN3, Folder 4)
        - Reviews, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box BN3, Folder 5)
        - Press, 1996-1997; 1 item
        - Miscellaneous, 1997; 1 item
          Letter from Charles Egleston and paperback cover art sample.
      - Essays, Reviews, and Introductions, 1970-1998; 1 item
        These files are only available via digitial access in the reading room.
        - Review: Kafka's Other Trial by Elias Canetti, undated; 1 item
        - "Where Are My White Sisters Now?", 1970s; 1 item
        - Letter to the Editor, 1971; 1 item
          Exchange with Jay David in response to Morrison's New York Times Book Review review of To Be a Black Woman: Portraits in Fact and Fiction.
        - Review: Birdy by William Wharton, circa 1978?; 1 item
        - Preface: The Harlem Book of the Dead by James Van Der Zee, 1978 April-August; 1 item
          With correspondence.
        - "Statistics", 1979 March 23; 1 item
        - Review: Labor of Love, Labor of Sorrow by Jacqueline Jones, 1985 April 14; 1 item
        - "A Knowing So Deep", 1985 May; 1 item
        - Preface: Two Wings to Veil My Face by Leon Forrest, 1987 January; 1 item
        - "More Thoughts on Death and the King's Horseman", 1987; 1 item
        - Foreword: Writing Red: An Anthology of American Women Writers 1930-1940, circa 1993; 1 item
          Incomplete.
        - "The Rapture", circa 1998; 1 item
          Introduction to A Kind of Rapture by Robert Bergman?
  - Phase 2: Plays, Musicals, Opera, 1980-2012; 15 boxes (1 partial)
    - Untitled Civil Rights Musical, undated; 1 folder (Box Plays1, Folder 1)
    - Julian, undated; 1 folder (Box Plays1, Folder 2)
    - The Way Widows Walk, undated; 1 folder (Box Plays1, Folder 3)
    - Recitatif, 1981; 1 folder (Box Plays1, Folder 4)
    - Garbo, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box Plays1, Folder 5)
    - Streetcar Named Desire Musical, 1995; 1 folder (Box Plays1, Folder 6)
    - New Orleans: The Storyville Musical, 1980-1984; 4 boxes
      Songs and lyrics, script notes and drafts with revisions, bound typescripts, NY Shakespeare Festival script and program, general correspondence, contracts, copyright registrations, and legal correspondence.
      - Early Draft Songs, 1982; 1 folder (Box NO1, Folder 1)
        These files only available via digital access.
      - Drafts of Lyrics, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box NO1, Folder 2)
      - Typed Drafts of Lyrics, 1982; 1 folder (Box NO1, Folder 3)
      - Willie Jeter, Lyrics and Music, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box NO1, Folder 4)
      - Notes I, 1982; 1 folder (Box NO1, Folder 5)
      - Notes II, 1982; 1 folder (Box NO1, Folder 6)
      - Notes 3, 1982; 1 folder (Box NO1, Folder 7)
      - Notes 4, 1982; 1 folder (Box NO1, Folder 8)
      - Notes 5, 1982; 1 folder (Box NO1, Folder 9)
      - Notes for Third Revision and Revised Draft, 1982; 1 folder (Box NO1, Folder 10)
      - Bound Scripts, 1982 January 14; 1 item (Box NO2, Folder 1)
      - Script with Revisions, 1982 June 8; 1 item (Box NO2, Folder 2)
      - Bound Scripts, 1982 June; 1 item (Box NO2, Folder 3)
      - Revised Script, 1984 June; 1 item (Box NO2, Folder 5)
        Fire-damaged and encapsulated.
      - New York Shakespeare Festival Script, circa 1984; 1 folder (Box NO2, Folder 6)
      - New York Shakespeare Festival Script "Version A", 1984 July 23; 1 item (Box NO3, Folder 1-2)
      - General Correspondence, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box NO4, Folder 1)
        Includes contact sheet.
      - Richard Greene Correspondence, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box NO4, Folder 2)
    - Dreaming Emmett, 1985-2005; 4 boxes
      Autograph, typescript and printout script drafts; production scripts, director's script, director and designer's notes, rehearsal notes, blocking notes, contact sheets, schedules, budgets, grant application, publicity, material re: proposed 1986 Festivel de Lilles production, general correspondence, legal and financial correspondence, essay relating to Emmett Till by Katherine Lederer, correspondence with director Gilbert Moses, including his notes on Act II and an analysis of the play, press clippings, photographs by Skip Dickstein.
      - Drafts, 1985-1986; 7 folders (Box DE1, Folder 1-7)
        These files are available only via digital access in the reading room.
      - Production Script, 1986 January 10; 1 item (Box DE2, Folder 1)
      - Production Material, 1985-1988; 3 folders (Box DE2, Folder 2-4)
        Production scripts, blocking notes, designer's notes, rehearsal notes, director's copy, essay by Elizabeth Adams. With letter from Lincoln Center Theater returning copy of script.
      - Designer's Notes, 1985; 1 folder (Box DE2, Folder 5)
      - Gilbert Moses Director's Notes, 1985; 1 folder (Box DE2, Folder 6)
      - Gilbert Moses, 1985; 1 folder (Box DE2, Folder 7)
        Includes "Quintet for the Old Man/Sketches of Harlem" draft, notes to Toni Morrison, "News Digest" historical summary of events surrounding Emmett Till's death, play analysis, and audition notes.
      - Research Material, 1 folder Annotated reproductions from microfilm, photocopied newspaper articles and photographs. (Box DE2, Folder 8)
      - Katherine Lederer, undated; 1 folder (Box DE2, Folder 9)
        Book chapter and article by Lederer on lyching.
      - "Dreaming Emmett Contact", 1985; 1 folder (Box DE2, Folder 10)
        Contact sheet, schedules, playbill.
      - Budgets and Contracts, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box DE2, Folder 11)
      - Capital Rep, 1 folder (Box DE2, Folder 12)
      - "Dreaming Emmett" binder, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box DE3, Folder 1)
        Includes press and performance schedules, Ruth Mott Fund Grant material, correspondence, and publicity file.
      - General Correspondence, 1985-2005; 1 folder (Box DE3, Folder 2)
      - Press, 1985-1988; 3 folders (Box DE3, Folder 3-5)
      - "Skip Dickstein Pix" [Photographs], 1986; 1 folder Black and white contact sheets and photographs, 2 color photographs, photocopies. (Box DE3, Folder 6)
        Signed Cynthia Morse.
      - "Photos and Miscellaneous", 1 folder (Box DE4, Folder 1)
        Binder containing photocopied research material and production photographs, contact sheet and rehearsal schedules.
      - Festival de Lille, 1986; 1 folder (Box DE4, Folder 2)
      - Requests, 1986-2004; 1 folder (Box DE4, Folder 3)
    - Margaret Garner, 1999-2008; 5 boxes
      Notes, story treatment, character sketches, synopses, drafts of libretto with revisions, libretto, piano vocal score, piano reduction, correspondence with composer Richard Danielpour and others, contracts, programs, press.
      - Treatment and Notes, circa 1999; 1 folder (Box MG1, Folder 1)
      - Drafts, circa 1999-2003; 2 folders (Box MG2, Folder 1-2, Box MG1, Folder 2-10)
        Boxes TK-TK only available via digital access.
        Autograph notepads and annotated printouts. One notepad includes drafts of Please, Louise.
      - Selections from Margaret Garner Piano Reduction, 2002 June 11; 1 item (Box MG3, Folder 1)
      - Act I, Scenes I & 2 Piano Reduction, 2003 February 4; 1 item (Box MG3, Folder 2)
      - Act I, Scenes 1 & 2 Piano Reduction, 2003 March 25; 1 item (Box MG3, Folder 3)
      - Act I, Scenes I & 2 Piano Reduction, 2003 April 2; 1 item (Box MG3, Folder 4)
      - Libretto, 2004 June 10; 1 item (Box MG3, Folder 5)
      - Piano Vocal Score--Act I, 2004 July 29; 1 item (Box MG3, Folder 6)
      - Piano Vocal Score--Act II, 2004 July 29; 1 item (Box MG3, Folder 7)
      - Piano Vocal Score, 2006 May 4; 1 folder (Box MG3, Folder 8)
      - Contracts, 2000; 1 folder (Box MG4, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1999-2004; 1 folder (Box MG4, Folder 2)
      - Cincinnati, 2005; 1 folder (Box MG4, Folder 3)
      - Detroit, 2005; 1 folder (Box MG4, Folder 4)
      - Philadelphia, 2006; 1 folder (Box MG4, Folder 5)
      - New York City Opera, 2007; 1 folder (Box MG4, Folder 6)
      - Chicago, 2008; 1 folder (Box MG4, Folder 7)
      - Publicity and Press, 2005; 1 folder (Box MG5, Folder 1, Box MG4, Folder 8)
      - Programs, 1 folder (Box MG5, Folder 2)
    - Desdemona, 2010-2012; more than 1 folder
      Correspondence and project description by director Peter Sellars, handwritten and typed notes and script drafts, production script with revisions.
      - Drafts, 15 folders (Box D1, Folder 1-15)
  - Phase 2: Poetry and Lyrics, 1984-2000; 3 boxes
    - Poetry, 1984-1986; portion of 1 folder (Box PL1, Folder 1)
      Includes "Nobody liked him," "Black Crazies," "You did alright, Girl," and "She is not seaworthy."
    - Honey and Rue, 1990-1996; 2 boxes (1 partial)
      Music by Andre Previn.
      - Lyrics, 1991-1995; portion of 1 folder (Box PL1, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1990-1996; 1 folder (Box PL1, Folder 2)
      - Scores, 1991; 1 box (Box PLoversize1, Box PL1, Folder 3-4)
        Inscribed to Morrison by Andre Previn and Kathleen Battle.
    - Four Songs, 1993-1996; 1 item
      Music by Andre Previn. With score.
      - Lyrics, 1993-1996; 1 item
      - Score, 1994; 1 item
    - Spirits in the Well, 1997; 1 item
      Music by Richard Danielpour.
    - Sweet Talk, 1995-1997; 1 item
      Music by Richard Danielpour. With score inscribed to Morrison by Richard Danielpour.
      - Lyrics and Program, 1995-1997; 1 item
      - Score, circa 1997; 1 item
        Inscribed to Morrison by Richard Danielpour.
    - woman.life.song, 2000; 1 item
      Music by Judith Weir.
    - This Thread, 1 item (Box PLoverize1)
  - Phase 2: Lectures and Speeches, 1979-2012; 1 box
    Arranged chronologically.
    Consists of notes, drafts with revisions, and final copies. Includes Tanner lecture "Unspeakable Things Unspoken" given at the University of Michigan (1988); Nobel speech drafts (1993); and Tanner lecture "The Loss of Lost Time" given at Cambridge (2000), as well as various commencement and inagural addresses, memorials and tributes, and introductory remarks. For the William E. Massey lectures given at Harvard in 1990, see Playing in the Dark.
    - Speeches I, 1979-1984; 1 item
    - Speeches II, 1981; 1 item
    - Speeches III, 1980-1983; 1 item
    - Speeches IV, 1981-1984; 1 item
    - Speeches V, 1984-1986; 1 item
    - Speech Fragments, 1989-2004; 1 item
    - BOMC Series on "Memoire", 1986; 1 item
    - NYPL, 1986; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Baldwin Eulogy, 1987; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - "Black Atlantic Art: Pencil of the Holy Ghost", 1988; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - "Unspeakable Things Unspoken" Tanner Lecture, 1988; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Nobel Lecture, 1993; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - The Dancing Mind, 1996; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - "The Trouble with Paradise", 1996; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - New York Public Library Address, 1997; 1 item
    - The Loss of Lost Time: Tanner Lecture at Cambridge, 2000; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Jacob Lawrence, 2000; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Slavebody/Blackbody--Milwaukee, 2000; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - June Jordan Introduction, 2000; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Literature and Public Life--Cornell University, 2000; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - What is a Good School? PEN--Washington DC, 2001; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Chinua Achebe Conversation, 2001; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - The Dead of September 11th--Princeton, 2001; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Smith Commencement, 2001; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Alice Randall/The Wind Done Gone Declamation, 2001; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Goodbye to All That--Radcliffe, 2001; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - She and Me--St. Jude's Anthology, 2002; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Simmons Business School Address, 2002; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Peter Sellars Intro--Sundance Institute, 2003; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Colorado College, 2004; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - John Hopkins Center African Studies Inaguration, 2004; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Nina Simone Tribute--Carnegie Hall, 2004; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Wellesley Commencement Speech, 2004; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - War Against Error--Edinburgh, 2004; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Peter Sellars Intro--Gish Award, 2005; portion of 1 box (Box S1)
    - Baccalaureate Address--Princeton, 2005; 1 item
    - Introduction of Vicky Colbert, Clinton Global Initiative Award Ceremony, 2007; 1 item
    - "The Past is Now", 2009; 1 item
    - ALA Convention Speech, 2010; 1 item
    - Draft: Feminist Legal Theory Conference, 2010; 1 item
    - Notes: Geneva, 2011; 1 item
    - Sackler Center First Awards, 2012; 1 item
  - Phase 2: Diaries and Logbooks, 1974-1997; 4 boxes (1 partial)
    This subseries is only available via digital access in the reading room.
    - Diary 1974, 1 item (Box D1)
    - Diary 1975, Number 1, 1 item (Box D1)
    - Diary 1975, Number 2, 1 item (Box D1)
    - Diary 1975, Number 3, 1 item (Box D1)
    - Diary 1976, Number 1, 1 item (Box D1)
    - Diary 1976, Number 2, 1 item (Box D1)
    - Diary 1977, 1 item (Box D1)
    - Diary 1978, 1 item (Box D2)
    - Diary 1979, 1 item (Box D4)
    - Diary 1980, 1 item (Box D2)
    - Diary 1980, 1 item (Box D4)
    - Diary 1981, 1 item (Box D4)
    - Diary 1981, 1 item (Box D2)
    - Diary 1982, 1 item (Box D2)
      Fire-damaged and encapsulated.Fire-damaged and encapsulated.
    - Diary 1982, 1 item (Box D4)
    - Diary 1983, 1 item (Box D2)
    - Diary 1983, 1 item (Box D2)
    - Diary 1983, 1 item (Box D4)
    - Diary 1987, 1 item (Box D3)
    - Diary 1989, 1 item (Box D3)
    - Diary 1991, 1 item (Box D4)
    - Diary 1992, 1 item (Box D4)
    - Diary 1993, 1 item (Box D4)
    - Diary 1994, 1 item (Box D4)
    - Diary 1994, 1 item (Box D4)
    - Planning Diary 1995, 1 item (Box D4)
    - Planning Diary 1996-1997, 1 item (Box D4)
    - Diary, Date Unknown, undated; 1 item (Box D3)
    - Diary, Date Unknown, undated; 1 item (Box D3)
    - Diary, Date Unknown, undated; 1 item (Box D3)
    - Logbook, 1975 July 8-November 21; 1 item (Box D3)
    - Logbook, 1975 November 17-1976 February 20; 1 item (Box D3)
    - Logbook, 1976 November 24-1977 February 17; 1 item (Box D3)
    - Logbook, 1977 February 18-May 11; 1 item (Box D4)
    - Logbook, 1977 May 12-August 8; 1 item (Box D4)
    - Telephone and Note Book, undated; 1 item (Box D4)
    - Pelure Cloquée Notebook, undated; 1 item (Box D4)
    - Milleraies Notebook, undated; 1 item (Box D4)
    - "Notes up to V. 1990", circa 1990; 1 item
  - Phase 2: Other Writings, 1958-2001; 1 item
    - Unidentified Writings, undated; 1 item
    - "Waiting for Disaster", undated; 1 item
    - Miscellaneous Drafts From Fire, undated; 1 item